A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14 FA286
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rochester Regional Plan, 4
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1471)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1472)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1473)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1474)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1475)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1944-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1476)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1477)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1478)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1479)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1480)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1481)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1482)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1483)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1484)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1485)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1946-1948 (Box 114, Folder 1486)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1487)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1488)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1489)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1490)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1491)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1492)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1493)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1494)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1495)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1496)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1497)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1498)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda, 1948-1957 (Box 115, Folder 1499)
  - General Correspondence and Memoranda Index, 1944-1952 (Box 116, Folder 1500)
  - Hospital Accounting Manual, March 31, 1945 (Box 116, Folder 1501)
  - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1502)
  - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1503)
  - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1504)
  - Interoffice Memoranda, 1943-1951 (Box 116, Folder 1505)
  - Local Survey - Bath Memorial Hospital, November 1948 (Box 116, Folder 1506)
  - Local Survey - Brockport Hospital Area, March 1947 (Box 116, Folder 1507)
  - Local Survey - Canadaigua Hospital Area, September 1947 (Box 116, Folder 1508)
  - Local Survey - Corning Hospital Area, April 1947 (Box 116, Folder 1509)
  - Local Survey - Dansville General Hospital, August 1946 (Box 116, Folder 1510)
  - Local Survey - Geneva Hospital Area, October 1947 (Box 116, Folder 1511)
  - Local Survey - Hornell Hospital Area, June 1946 (Box 116, Folder 1512)
  - Local Survey - Penn Yan Hospital Area, November 1946 (Box 116, Folder 1513)
  - Local Survey - Shepard Relief Hospital, October 1948 (Box 117, Folder 1514)
  - Local Survey - Summaries (Batavia to Wellsville), June 1945 (Box 117, Folder 1515)
  - Medical Records Manual Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) (Section 1 Unit Number System), November 1948 (Box 117, Folder 1516)
  - Minutes, n.d. (Box 117, Folder 1517)
    Administrators Conference - June 19, 1946-June 30, 1948 Admission and Maintenance of Membership Committee - June 27, 1947-July 28, 1948 Capital Grants Committee - February 1, 1948-December 19, 1950
  - Minutes, n.d. (Box 117, Folder 1518)
    Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) - February 26, 1946-May 11, 1948 Medical Conference - November 1947
  - News Bulletin - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), 1946-1948; 1959-1962 (Box 117, Folder 1519)
  - Personnel Survey - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), December 1950 (Box 117, Folder 1520)
  - Plan of Action For the Future - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), 1950 (Box 117, Folder 1521)
  - Principles Governing Capital Grants, November 12, 1947 (Box 117, Folder 1522)
  - Publications - Forms and Reprints, 1945-1950 (Box 117, Folder 1523)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 117, Folder 1524)
  - Quarterly Reports, 1946-1947 (Box 117, Folder 1525)
  - Reports and Surveys - Annual Report - Community Nursing Council, 1949-1950 (Box 117, Folder 1526)
  - Reports and Surveys - Background and Reference Material - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), May 7, 1948 (Box 117, Folder 1527)
  - Reports and Surveys - Community Health and Medical Care Statistics by Hospital District - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), November 12, 1947 (Box 117, Folder 1528)
  - Reports and Surveys - Educational Questionnaire and Course Outlines, 1947-1951 (Box 117, Folder 1529)
  - Reports and Surveys - Facts and Figures About CRRH Hospitals, December 1948 (Box 117, Folder 1530)
  - Reports and Surveys - Hospital Construction Needs and Progress Made Toward Meeting Such Needs - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), April 1, 1948 (Box 117, Folder 1531)
  - Reports and Surveys - Hospital Construction Needs and Recommendations for Capital Grants to be Made by Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), December 1, 1948 (Box 118, Folder 1532)
  - Reports and Surveys - Miscellaneous Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) Cost Procedure Papers, 1947-1950 (Box 118, Folder 1533)
  - Reports and Surveys - Nursing-Hour Studies, 1946-1949, 1951 (Box 118, Folder 1534)
  - Requisitions, 1946-1952 (Box 118, Folder 1535)
  - Requisitions, 1946-1952 (Box 118, Folder 1536)
  - Requisitions, 1946-1952 (Box 118, Folder 1537)
  - Requisitions, 1946-1952 (Box 118, Folder 1538)
  - Requisitions, 1946-1952 (Box 118, Folder 1539)
  - Rules and Regulations - Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH), March-October, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 1540)
  - Standards for Admission and Maintenance of Council of Rochester Regional Hospitals (CRRH) Membership, June 27, 1947 (Box 118, Folder 1541)
  - Statistics - Medical and Hospital, 1940-1950 (Box 118, Folder 1542)